[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "01_SoleSurvivor",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "01_SoleSurvivor_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "01_SoleSurvivor2",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Sole Survivor",
        "Description": "Captain Thorpe lost the mysterious box at sea and now appears to have perished... but his corpse disintegrated. Find out what happened to him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Are we the only survivors?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I think so... I could've sworn I saw one of the swabbies, but it was one of those... creatures. \\n\\nDamned priest! I never should've trusted that bastard - all his talk of legends and power, treasures... nothing but lies. \\n\\nAnd the box he gave meâ€¦",
        "InProgressResponse": "Find out what happened to Captain Thorpe.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "n/a",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "01_SoleSurvivor2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "01_SoleSurvivor2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Sole Survivor",
        "Description": "Captain Thorpe has been consumed by Corruption. You must defeat him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Accept the Quest",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_getoffbeach_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_ww",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Sole Survivor",
        "Description": "This is a test",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you have food and supplies?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Unfortunately, we don't keep the watchtower very well stocked. \"Bring your own mead,\" is the rule. \\n\\nBut there are some nice, fat boar roaming around nearby... of course, you're not exactly equipped for hunting, are you?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Flint, wood, skinning knife. Then we're good to go.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Steady there, friend. Dying can be a rather harrowing experience the first time one goes through it. \\n\\nYou're actually looking quite... healthy, all things considered. Luckier than most!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_getoffbeach_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Sole Survivor",
        "Description": "This is a test",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you have food and supplies?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Unfortunately, we don't keep the watchtower very well stocked. \"Bring your own mead,\" is the rule. \\n\\nBut there are some nice, fat boar roaming around nearby... of course, you're not exactly equipped for hunting, are you?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Flint, wood, skinning knife. Then we're good to go.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Steady there, friend. Dying can be a rather harrowing experience the first time one goes through it. \\n\\nYou're actually looking quite... healthy, all things considered. Luckier than most!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_skinningknife",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_skinningknife_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_skinningknife",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_ww",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_skinningknife_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Basic Needs",
        "Description": "Gather Flint and Wood, craft a Flint Skinning Knife at the Watcher's Campfire, and then talk to Watcher Reese.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you have food and supplies?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Unfortunately, we don't keep the watchtower very well stocked. \"Bring your own mead,\" is the rule. \\n\\nBut there are some nice, fat boar roaming around nearby... of course, you're not exactly equipped for hunting, are you?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Flint, wood, skinning knife. Then we're good to go.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Very impressive! One of the nicest crude skinning knives I've seen. \\n\\nYou've done this before, haven't you?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_skinningknife",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_skinningknife_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_skinningknife_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_skinningknife_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Basic Needs",
        "Description": "Gather Flint and Wood, craft a Flint Skinning Knife at the Watcher's Campfire, and then talk to Watcher Reese.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you have food and supplies?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Unfortunately, we don't keep the watchtower very well stocked. \"Bring your own mead,\" is the rule. \\n\\nBut there are some nice, fat boar roaming around nearby... of course, you're not exactly equipped for hunting, are you?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Flint, wood, skinning knife. Then we're good to go.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Very impressive! One of the nicest crude skinning knives I've seen. \\n\\nYou've done this before, haven't you?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_boarfeast",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_boarfeast_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarfeast",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_skinningknife",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_boarfeast_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Campfire Feast",
        "Description": "Hunt and skin a boar, make some light rations at the Watcher's campfire, and then talk to Watcher Reese.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is that the town you came from?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, it has its own share of troubles, but nothing like what we're seeing here. The persistence of this storm is worrisome, to say the least. \\n\\nI may very well need your help, but as I promised, we need to get you fed first.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Mmmâ€¦ boar.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Mmm, that smells delicious, and you seem to be feeling better than when you first rejoined the ranks of the living. \\n\\nThat's convenient, because I really do need your help to make sure the threat here on the shore is contained.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_boarfeast",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_boarfeast_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarfeast_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_skinningknife_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_boarfeast_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Campfire Feast",
        "Description": "Hunt and skin a boar, make some light rations at the Watcher's campfire, and then talk to Watcher Reese.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is that the town you came from?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, it has its own share of troubles, but nothing like what we're seeing here. The persistence of this storm is worrisome, to say the least. \\n\\nI may very well need your help, but as I promised, we need to get you fed first.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Mmmâ€¦ boar.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Mmm, that smells delicious, and you seem to be feeling better than when you first rejoined the ranks of the living. \\n\\nThat's convenient, because I really do need your help to make sure the threat here on the shore is contained.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_crewmates",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_crewmates_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_crewmates",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_boarfeast",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_crewmates_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Crewmates No More",
        "Description": "Defeat your Corrupted Crewmates and try to put them back to rest.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What does it mean to be Corrupted?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That's the dark side of eternal life, I suppose. You resurrected with your soul intact, but many come back soulless, the \"Lost.\" \\n\\nOr worse, they return with their souls twisted, possessed by insatiable evil. Those we call the \"Corrupted.\"",
        "InProgressResponse": "I know it's not easy, but it really is the right thing.\\n\\nThink of it as a mercy - that's what I do.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well done. It's grim work, I know, but we can't let the Corrupted get entrenched down here. \\n\\nUnfortunately, their numbers seem to just keep growingâ€¦ several shipwrecks along the shore, and more by the hour.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_crewmates",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_crewmates_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_crewmates_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_boarfeast_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_crewmates_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Crewmates No More",
        "Description": "Defeat your Corrupted Crewmates and try to put them back to rest.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What does it mean to be Corrupted?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That's the dark side of eternal life, I suppose. You resurrected with your soul intact, but many come back soulless, the \"Lost.\" \\n\\nOr worse, they return with their souls twisted, possessed by insatiable evil. Those we call the \"Corrupted.\"",
        "InProgressResponse": "I know it's not easy, but it really is the right thing.\\n\\nThink of it as a mercy - that's what I do.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well done. It's grim work, I know, but we can't let the Corrupted get entrenched down here. \\n\\nUnfortunately, their numbers seem to just keep growingâ€¦ several shipwrecks along the shore, and more by the hour.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_survivors",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_survivors_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceWW_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_survivors",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_crewmates",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_06_survivors_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Amidst the Wreckage",
        "Description": "Search the shipwrecks for survivors and take out as many Corrupted as you can. Return to the Watchtower when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Who could be causing it?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm not sure, but all this wreckage at the same time, it seems like it must be coordinated somehow. \\n\\nWe generally see a new shipwreck only once a season, and even then, there are usually more survivors.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you find anyone, send them this way. \\n\\nAnd for pity's sake, watch your back out there. Don't need you becoming Corrupted as well.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well now, can't tell you what a relief it was seeing someone who was still human. \\n\\nI was beginning to think I was all alone out hereâ€¦ the rest of the world had gone mad.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_survivors",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_survivors_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceMB_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_survivors_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_crewmates_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_survivors_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Amidst the Wreckage",
        "Description": "Search the shipwrecks for survivors and take out as many Corrupted as you can. Return to the Watchtower when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Who could be causing it?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm not sure, but all this wreckage at the same time, it seems like it must be coordinated somehow. \\n\\nWe generally see a new shipwreck only once a season, and even then, there are usually more survivors.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you find anyone, send them this way. \\n\\nAnd for pity's sake, watch your back out there. Don't need you becoming Corrupted as well.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well now, can't tell you what a relief it was seeing someone who was still human. \\n\\nI was beginning to think I was all alone out hereâ€¦ the rest of the world had gone mad.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_pillageship",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_pillageship_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_pillageship",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_survivors",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_06_pillageship_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Lessons of a Pirate's Life",
        "Description": "Search the shipwreck for a manifest and locate the valuable items on the list. Find and speak to Grace O'Malley when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You're looting these ships?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Of course. Not like these rotters care a damn for it, and I'll be needing a new ship, a new crewâ€¦ that takes coin. \\n\\nIn fact, if you want to partner up, I'll split the loot 70-30, or what the hell, 60-40 even! What do you say? Then we can go head to that watchtower of yours.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Well now, we aren't getting any younger, are we? \\n\\nLet's grab it while we can.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There you are - I was starting to worry. More importantly, though - what did you find? \\n\\nLet's see here... Ooh, yes, these are definitely worth a coin or two. Soon as we find a town, we'll sell them and split the profit.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_pillageship",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_pillageship_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_pillageship_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_survivors_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_pillageship_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Lessons of a Pirate's Life",
        "Description": "Search the shipwreck for a manifest and locate the valuable items on the list. Find and speak to Grace O'Malley when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You're looting these ships?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Of course. Not like these rotters care a damn for it, and I'll be needing a new ship, a new crewâ€¦ that takes coin. \\n\\nIn fact, if you want to partner up, I'll split the loot 70-30, or what the hell, 60-40 even! What do you say? Then we can go head to that watchtower of yours.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Well now, we aren't getting any younger, are we? \\n\\nLet's grab it while we can.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There you are - I was starting to worry. More importantly, though - what did you find? \\n\\nLet's see here... Ooh, yes, these are definitely worth a coin or two. Soon as we find a town, we'll sell them and split the profit.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_recoveritems",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_recoveritems_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_recoveritems",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_pillageship",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_06_recoveritems_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Memories of Grace",
        "Description": "Search the shipwrecks for survivors and take out as many Corrupted as you can. Return to the Watchtower when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You want me to try?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Now, there's a good mate. Tough one too, if you're so confident. No complaints, though. \\n\\nTell you what, if you can get my stuff back, I'll give you a greater share of our profits, 40-60... or what the hell? 30-70. What do you say?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Your watcher friend there really wants a word with you. \\n\\nYou should talk to him first.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome back, my friend. Glad to see you're still with us. I was elated to meet another survivor, but I feared we'd lost you in the process. \\n\\nGrace O'Malley, a real piece of work, isn't she? Can't say I would've wanted to make that trade.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_recoveritems",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_recoveritems_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_recoveritems_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_pillageship_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_recoveritems_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Memories of Grace",
        "Description": "Search the shipwrecks for survivors and take out as many Corrupted as you can. Return to the Watchtower when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You want me to try?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Now, there's a good mate. Tough one too, if you're so confident. No complaints, though. \\n\\nTell you what, if you can get my stuff back, I'll give you a greater share of our profits, 40-60... or what the hell? 30-70. What do you say?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Your watcher friend there really wants a word with you. \\n\\nYou should talk to him first.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome back, my friend. Glad to see you're still with us. I was elated to meet another survivor, but I feared we'd lost you in the process. \\n\\nGrace O'Malley, a real piece of work, isn't she? Can't say I would've wanted to make that trade.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_demonstorm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_demonstorm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_recoveritems",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Team Effort",
        "Description": "Talk to Grace O'Malley and then meet Watcher Reese near the entrance to the sea caves.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should check it out.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "See? Now there's someone willing to step up. I can't do this alone. \\n\\nI thought perhaps our new friend might join as well, but she's not really the joining type, is she?",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll be waiting for you by the entrance to the sea caves. \\n\\nDon't waste too much time on a lost cause, eh.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hey, you gave it a try, at least. That Grace O'Malley's a pirate to the bone. Doesn't care about anyone but herself. \\n\\nLooking at the Corrupted massing here, however, neither her nor anyone else will be safe, if this keeps up.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_demonstorm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_demonstorm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_recoveritems_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Team Effort",
        "Description": "Talk to Grace O'Malley and then meet Watcher Reese near the entrance to the sea caves.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We should check it out.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "See? Now there's someone willing to step up. I can't do this alone. \\n\\nI thought perhaps our new friend might join as well, but she's not really the joining type, is she?",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll be waiting for you by the entrance to the sea caves. \\n\\nDon't waste too much time on a lost cause, eh.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hey, you gave it a try, at least. That Grace O'Malley's a pirate to the bone. Doesn't care about anyone but herself. \\n\\nLooking at the Corrupted massing here, however, neither her nor anyone else will be safe, if this keeps up.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_demonstorm2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_demonstorm2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Demon Storm",
        "Description": "Search the Sea Caves and destroy anything that might be the source of the Corruption Storm. Report back to Watcher Reese at the Watchtower when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Ready to go in?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I don't know. If we both fall in there, there'll be no one to get word to town. I certainly don't trust that pirate to do so. \\n\\nI say we head back to town and recruit as many sword-arms as we can, and then come back.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Be careful in there. And remember - I didn't ask you to do this, you volunteered!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "God's teeth! When I saw the storm receding, I knew you had triumphed!\\n\\nWhat was in there? Some kind of abomination? A Corruption Rift? I've heard legends of such things from way back.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_demonstorm2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_demonstorm2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm2_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Demon Storm",
        "Description": "Search the Sea Caves and destroy anything that might be the source of the Corruption Storm. Report back to Watcher Reese at the Watchtower when you're done.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Ready to go in?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I don't know. If we both fall in there, there'll be no one to get word to town. I certainly don't trust that pirate to do so. \\n\\nI say we head back to town and recruit as many sword-arms as we can, and then come back.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Be careful in there. And remember - I didn't ask you to do this, you volunteered!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "God's teeth! When I saw the storm receding, I knew you had triumphed!\\n\\nWhat was in there? Some kind of abomination? A Corruption Rift? I've heard legends of such things from way back.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_raisealarm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_raisealarm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_MarcelDupont01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_raisealarm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Bearer of Bad Tidings",
        "Description": "Travel to the town of Corinth and deliver the Watcher's report.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you think it's happening again?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I suspect we'll see more Corrupted in the future, but let's hope we can prevent such darkness as the legends speak of. \\n\\nStill, I'll write a report for the town, tell them the storm's receded, but to remain vigilant.",
        "InProgressResponse": "When you get to town, reward yourself with a cup of mead at the tavern. \\n\\nYou deserve it, my friend.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hold up there, what business do you have in Corinth? A report from the Watcher, eh? OK, I'll take that. \\n\\nSo it was Corruption causing that hellish storm. Merde! Don't we have enough problems?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_raisealarm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_raisealarm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_raisealarm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Bearer of Bad Tidings",
        "Description": "Travel to the town of Prydwen and deliver the Watcher's report.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you think it's happening again?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I suspect we'll see more Corrupted in the future, but let's hope we can prevent such darkness as the legends speak of. \\n\\nStill, I'll write a report for the town, tell them the storm's receded, but to remain vigilant.",
        "InProgressResponse": "When you get to town, reward yourself with a cup of mead at the tavern. \\n\\nYou deserve it, my friend.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome to Prydwen, founded during the reign of the High King, a legacy honored to this day! \\n\\nAh, a report from Watcher Reese? Thank you! Hm. So it was foul Corruption behind the storm? Very well. I will dispatch a Knight straightaway.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0625_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0625_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistWW_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles_ww",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0625_0101_truffles_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Truffle Fever",
        "Description": "Collect any Truffles you can find in the forest and bring them to Hapless Howe in the settlement. Look for any Herbs or Berries you can gather as well.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why would they do that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "How should I know? Do I look like some kind of \"boar-mind-reader\"? Not me. I'm just a simple Traveling Herbalist.\\n\\nTell you this much, however, the beasts have ruined me for the season.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Sad days are these when a traveling Herbalist has to rely on the goodwill of a stranger to make ends meet.\\n\\nBut if you'll bring me some truffles in the settlement, I'll have a little something for you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Here's my new friend, right here! All the truffles I lost and then some! I hope it wasn't too hard!\\n\\nKeep that sickle for your troubles, and if you make a habit of Harvesting herbs and such, we'll cross paths again, no doubt.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1225_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1225_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistMB_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1225_0101_truffles_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Truffle Fever",
        "Description": "Collect any Truffles you can find in the forest and bring them to Hapless Howe in the settlement. Look for any Herbs or Berries you can gather as well.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why would they do that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "How should I know? Do I look like some kind of \"boar-mind-reader\"? Not me. I'm just a simple Traveling Herbalist.\\n\\nTell you this much, however, the beasts have ruined me for the season.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Sad days are these when a traveling Herbalist has to rely on the goodwill of a stranger to make ends meet.\\n\\nBut if you'll bring me some truffles in the settlement, I'll have a little something for you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Here's my new friend, right here! All the truffles I lost and then some! I hope it wasn't too hard!\\n\\nKeep that sickle for your troubles, and if you make a habit of Harvesting herbs and such, we'll cross paths again, no doubt.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
